AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XVIII: Consolidations, Mergers, Reorganizations and Abandonments, 1938-1970
  - Rutland Railway Corp. - Abandonment, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311-2128, pt. 1; Dec. 8, 1961 - Sept. 24, 1963
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Merger - New York Central Railroad, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-311-2155, pt. 1; Jan. 10, 1962 - Jun. 26, 1963
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Merger - New York Central Railroad, 1963-1967 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-311-2155, pt. 2; Jul. 1, 1963 - Jul. 20, 1967
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Merger - New York Central Railroad, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-2155, pt. 3; Aug. 8, 1967 - Dec. 30, 1968
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Merger - New York Central Railroad, 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311-2155, pt. 4; Dec. 30, 1968 - Nov. 23, 1970(?)
  - National Defense Program - Railway Industry Comm., 1940 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-328, pt. 1; May 8, 1940 - Dec. 30, 1940
  - National Defense Program - Railway Industry Comm., 1941 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-328, pt. 2; Jan. 7, 1941 - Aug. 29, 1941
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Comp. Case, 1941-1957 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-328; Jul. 18, 1941 - Oct. 16, 1957
  - Cincinnati Union Terminal Railroad, 1941-1953 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-328; May 19, 1941 - Jan. 27, 1953
  - Denver and Salt Lake Railroad, 1942-1947 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-328; Sept. 17, 1942 - Nov. 12, 1947
  - Defense Transportation - Office of Co-ordination, 1941-1943 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-328-E, pt. 1; Dec. 29, 1941 - Oct. 21, 1943
  - Office of Defense Transportation, 1944-1952 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-328-E, pt. 2; Jan. 24, 1944 - Jul. 30, 1952
  - Office of Defense Transportation, 1941-1942 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    Code no. 35-328-E, Comm., pt. 1; Dec. 29, 1941 - Nov. 30, 1942
  - Office of Defense Transportation, 1942-1943 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    Code no. 35-328-E, Comm., pt. 2; Dec. 3, 1942 - Mar. 29, 1943
  - National War Labor Board, 1942-1944 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-328-F, pt. 1; Jan. 16, 1942 - Sept. 24, 1943
  - War Production Board - Correspondence, 1942-1961 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-328-H, pt. 1; Jan. 25, 1942 - Aug. 25, 1944
  - President's Committee on Fair Employment Practice, 1942-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-328-I, pt. 1; Jan 31., 1942 - Jun. 27, 1961
  - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1943 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-328-K, pt. 1; Apr. 28, 1942 - Oct. 28, 1943
  - War Manpower Commission, 1943-1946 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-328-K, pt. 2; Nov. 3, 1943 - Dec. 27, 1946
  - Part 1 of this file charged to B.M. Jewell, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-328-K-Comm., pt. 1; Jul. 8, 1942 - never returned
  - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1943 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-328-K-Comm., pt. 2; Apr. 18, 1942 - Mar. 31, 1943
  - War Manpower Commission, 1943 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-328-K-Comm., pt. 3; Apr. 1, 1943 - Aug. 16, 1943
  - Digest of War Manpower Commission, 1943 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-328-K-Comm. May
  - Selective Service Act, 1940-1944 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-333, pt. 1; Jul. 30, 1940 - Jun. 23, 1944
  - Selective Service Act, 1944-1945 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    Code No. 35-333, pt. 2; Jul. 8, 1944 - Aug. 23, 1945
  - Selective Service Act, 1945-1947 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-333, pt. 3; Sept. 1, 1945 - May 28, 1947
  - Selective Service Act, 1947-1951 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-333, pt. 4; Jun. 2, 1947 - Dec. 26, 1951
  - Denver and Salt Lake Railroad (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-333
  - Shreveport Joint Car Inspection and Interchange Bureau - Abandoned, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-333; Aug. 2, 1946
  - Selective Service Act, 1942-1946 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-333, Comm., pt. 1; Jan. 29, 1942 - Feb. 26, 1946
  - Office of Defense Transportation - Railway Manpower, 1942 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-410, pt. 1; Jun. 11, 1942 - May 29, 1942
  - Office of Defense Transportation - Railway Manpower, 1944-1952 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-410, pt. 2; Jun. 16, 1944 - Jul. 21, 1952
  - Employment of Mexican Nationals, 1942-1956 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-410-A; Jun. 18, 1942 - Nov. 15, 1956
  - Office of Defense Transportation - Railway Manpower, 1942-1943 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    Code No. 35-410, Comm., pt. 1; Jun. 11, 1942 - Jul. 30, 1943
  - Physically Handicapped and Vocational Rehabilitation, 1943-1953 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-414; Jun. 23, 1943 - Sept. 21, 1953
  - Physically Handicapped and Vocational Rehabilitation, 1943-1961 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-414, pt. 2; Oct. 4, 1953 - Nov. 26, 1961
  - Stabilizing Wages - Price Control - Executive Order 9250, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-423, pt. 1; May 26, 1943 - Nov. 24, 1943
  - Stabilization Act of 1942, 1944-1948 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-423, pt. 2; Jan. 5, 1944 - Feb. 9, 1948
  - Occupational Safety, 1944-1966 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-473, pt. 1; Mar. 30, 1944 - May 19, 1966
  - Senate Joint Resolution 91, 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-478, pt. 1; Nov. 30, 1943 - Jul. 17, 1944
  - G.I. Bill of Rights - Educational Aids, 1944-1946 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-484, pt. 1; Mar. 27, 1944 - Jul. 29, 1946
  - G.I. Bill of Rights - Servicemen's Readjustment Act, 1944-1951 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-484, pt. 2; Aug. 7, 1946 - Jun. 29, 1951
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Case No. 13528 - Investigation of power brakes and appliances for operation power brake system, 1944-1965 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-487, pt. 1; Aug. 3, 1944 - Mar. 24, 1965
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1944-1947 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-493, pt. 1; Jul. 31, 1944 - Feb. 27, 1947
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1947-1962 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-493, pt. 2; Mar. 14, 1947 - May 2, 1962
  - Committee on Post Office and Civil Service - Railway Mail Transportation, 1948-1965 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-549, pt. 1; Jul. 27, 1948 - Dec. 2, 1965
  - Modification of U.S. Safety Appliance Standards, Union Tank Car Co., 1957-1963 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-608, pt. 1; Nov. 1, 1957 - Oct. 30, 1963
  - Landrum-Griffin Labor Bill (Labor Disclosure Act of 1959), 1958-1960 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-636, pt. 1; Oct. 19, 1958 - Apr. 26, 1960
  - Landrum-Griffin Labor Bill (Labor Disclosure Act of 1959), 1960-1965 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-626, pt. 2; Jun. 1, 1960 - Feb. 11, 1965
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Protest and Request for Suspension, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-636, pt. 1; Jun. 21, 1961 - Oct. 29, 1962
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Protest and Request for Suspension, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-636, pt. 2; Nov. 6, 1962 - Dec. 27, 1963
- Series XIX: Co-Operation - Financial Matters, Minutes, Proceedings and Correspondence, 1919-1933
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), reports, proposals, critiques, appraisals, financial records (pro-rated bills and receipts}, minutes, and contracts regarding the Cooperative Movement within the railroad industry. More specifically, the Baltimore a
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees of Chillicothe, Ohio Shops, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 19, 1924 - Mar. 7, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Cleveland Terminal Shops, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1925 - Mar. 4, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Cone Shops, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Flora, Illinois, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1925 - Mar. 19, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Garret, Indiana, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1925 - 18, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Hamilton, Ohio, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1925 - Mar. 18, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Dayton, Ohio, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    Code No. 36-2; Mar. 24, 1924 - Mar. 6, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Ivorydale, Ohio, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Lima, Ohio, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    Code No. 36-2; Mar. 19, 1924 - Mar. 7, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Storrs, Ohio, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    Code No. 36-2; Feb. 18, 1925 - Mar. 20, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Mount Clare Shops, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    Code No. 36- 2; Jan. 7, 1925 - Mar. 4, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, New Castle Junction, Pennsylvania, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1925 - Mar. 6, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Newark Shop, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 21, 1925 - Mar. 4, 1925
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Toledo, Ohio, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Willard, Ohio, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of meeting of Co-operative plan between management and employees, Zanesville, Ohio, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    Code No. 36-2; Jan. 7, 1924 - Mar. 18, 1925
  - Withdrawal of Machinist from Co-operative meetings at Cumberland, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    Code No. 36-2; Jul. 25, 1925 - Aug. 3, 1925
  - Philadelphia - Activities of System Federation - Executive Board on Wage and Rule Conference, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    Code No. 36-2; Jul. 29, 1925 - Aug. 31, 1925
  - Miscellaneous material on union management co-operation (Box 88, Folder 19)
    Code No. 36-2
  - Co-operation Financial - Pro-rated Bills - O.S. Beyer, Jr., 1923-1926 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    Code No. 36-2A; Jul. 26, 1923 - May 10, 1926
  - Co-operation Financial - Pro-rated Bills - O.S. Beyer, Jr., 1926-1930 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    Code No. 36-2-A, pt. 2; May 8, 1926 - Dec. 16, 1930
  - Co-operation Financial - Pro-rated Bills - O.S. Beyer, Jr., 1931-1947 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    Code No. 36-2-A, pt. 3; Jan. 5, 1931 - Apr. 9, 1947
  - Baltimore and Ohio Co-op - Maintenance of Way, 1931 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    Code No. 36-2-A-2; Jun. 19, 1931 - Jul. 23, 1931
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and Saint Paul Railroad Co-operation, 1923-1933 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Code No. 36-4; Nov. 24, 1923 - Apr. 18, 1933
  - Canadian National Co-operation, 1924-1930 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Code No. 36-6, pt. 1; Jan. 17, 1924 - Dec. 29, 1930
  - Canadian Maintenance of Way Co-operation, 1924-1932 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Code No. 36-6-A-2; Aug. 23, 1924 - Jul. 27, 1932
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Co-operation, 1924-1933 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Code No. 36-8; Apr. 21, 1924 - Dec. 6, 1933
  - Seaboard Air Line Co-operation, 1924-1931 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Code No. 36-12; May 15, 1924 - Nov. 10, 1931
  - Shipley Company - Contractors with Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railway Co., 1943-1956 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    Code No. 38-59; Jan. 12, 1943 - Nov. 26, 1956
  - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Code No. 3C-180; Sept. 14, 1922 - Oct. 21, 1922
  - Minnesota Transfer Railway, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Code No. 3C-181; Sept. 14, 1922 - Mar. 26, 1923
  - Copper Range Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Code No. 3C-182; Sept. 14, 1922 - Oct. 23, 1923
  - St. Paul Union Depot Company, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Code No. 3C-183; Sept. 14, 1922 - Apr. 3, 1923
  - St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Company, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Code No. 3C-184; Sept. 14, 1922 - Oct. 21, 1922
  - Minnesota, Dakota and Western Railway, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Code No. 3C-185; Sept. 14, 1922 - Apr. 5, 1923
  - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad, 1922-1924 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    Code No. 3C-186; Sept. 16, 1922 - Apr. 8, 1924
  - Union Stock Yards Railroad, 1922-1924 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    Code No. 3C-187; Sept. 14, 1922 - Feb. 4, 1924
  - Western Alabama Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    Code No. 3C-188; Sept. 18, 1922 - May 7, 1923
  - Ulster and Delaware Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    Code No. 3C-189; Sept. 8, 1922 - May 25, 1923
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    Code No. 3C-190; Sept. 21, 1922 - Mar. 28, 1923
  - Boston Terminal Company, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    Code No. 3C-191; Sept. 29, 1922 - Dec. 3, 1923
  - Tonopah, Tide Water and Death Valley Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    Code No. 3C-192; Sept. 29, 1922 - Oct. 12, 1922
  - Houston Belt Terminal Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    Code No. 3C-193; Oct. 11, 1922 - Oct. 16, 1922
  - Duluth South Shore and Atlantic Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    Code No. 3C-194; Oct. 12, 1922 - Oct. 24, 1922
  - Sioux City Terminal Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    Code No. 3C-195; Oct. 6, 1922 - Oct. 18, 1922
  - Ft. Dodge, Des Moines, Southern Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    Code No. 3C-196; Oct. 23, 1922 - Oct. 24, 1922
  - Quanah Acme and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    Code No. 3C-197; Nov. 13, 1922 - Apr. 18, 1923
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    Code No. 3C-198; Oct. 24, 1922 - Jul. 11, 1923
  - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    Code No. 3C-199; Dec. 11, 1922 - Mar. 30, 1923
  - Galveston, Houston and Henderson and Galveston Wharf Company Railways, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    Code No. 3C-200; Dec. 24, 1922 - Mar. 14, 1923
  - Memphis Union Station Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    Code No. 3C-201; Jan. 20, 1923
  - Blue Ridge Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    Code No. 3C-203; Apr. 18, 1923 - Jul. 9, 1923
  - Morgan Engineering Company, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    Code No. 3C-204; Nov. 15, 1922 - Aug. 30, 1923
  - Waco, Beaumont, Trinity and Sabine Railway, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    Code No. 3C-205; Apr. 21, 1923 - Apr. 24, 1923
  - Indianapolis Belt Railroad, 1923-1924 (Box 111, Folder 26)
    Code No. 3C-206; Mar. 1, 1923 - Apr. 15, 1924
  - Dallas Terminal Railway, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 27)
    Code No. 3C-207; May 11, 1923 - Jul. 5, 1923
  - Savannah and Atlanta Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 28)
    Code No. 3C-208; Mar. 5, 1923 - Oct. 18, 1923
  - Davenport Locomotive Works, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 29)
    Code No. 3C-209; Jul. 14, 1923 - Aug. 3, 1923
  - Midland Valley Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    Code No. 3C-210; Sept. 30, 1922 - Oct. 22, 1923
  - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    Code No. 3C-211; Sept. 13, 1923 - Oct. 3, 1923
  - Cleveland Crane and Engineering Company, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    Code No. 3C-212; Feb. 20, 1923 - Oct. 25, 1923
  - Wrightsville and Tennille Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 33)
    Code No. 3C-213; Oct. 30, 1923 - Dec. 11, 1923
  - Union Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 34)
    Code No. 3C-214; Nov. 2, 1923 - Nov. 6, 1923
  - St. Louis Refrigerator Car Company, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    Code No. 3C-215; Nov. 19, 1923 - Dec. 20, 1923
  - New Jersey, Indiana and Illinois Railroad, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 36)
    Code No. 3C-216; Dec. 10, 1923 - Dec. 14, 1923
- Series XXIII: National Rules and Working Conditions Agreements Between Employees Represented by the Railway Employees Department of the AFL and Carriers Under the Provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920 - Correspondence, Etc., 1920-1934
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), minutes, agreements, legal documents (dockets, briefs), proceedings, publications, and clippings regarding disputes over national agreements; applications to the United States Railway Labor Board for decisions; on v
  - Other organizations - Rule 3, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - Southern Pacific Lines, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 38)
    Mar. 30
  - National Agreement Committee - Division 1, 2, and 3, Railway Employees' Department, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 39)
    Aug. 22-24
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway - Electrical Workers, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 40)
    Code No. MC-26-14-1; Jan. 29, 1921 - Apr. 1, 1921
  - Michigan Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 41)
    Code No. MC-224-14-4; Feb. 13, 1921 - Feb. 21, 1921
  - Ft. Dodge, Des Moines, Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 42)
    Code No. MC-363-14-5; Feb. 13, 1921 - Feb. 18, 1921
  - Minutes of meeting of Chief Executives Standard Recognized Railroad Labor Organizations, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 43)
    Code No. MC-0-14-6; Feb. 18-21
  - Application of the National Agreement of Salem, Oregon, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 44)
    Code No. MC-157-14-7; Mar. 1, Mar. 25
  - Dispute between Pere Marquette Railroad and Clerks' Organization in re: Addenda Clerks' National Agreement, 1920-1921 (Box 111, Folder 45)
    Code No. MC-130-14-8; Dec. 28, 1920 - Mar. 11, 1921
  - Forwarding Special Delivery Letter to E.H. Fitzgerald - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 46)
    Code No. MC-157-14-10; Mar. 23
  - Southern Pacific System Federation, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 47)
    Code No. MC-157-14-14; Mar. 19, 1921 - Apr. 1, 1921
  - I.C. East St. Louis Railroad, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 48)
    Code No. MC-74-14-15; Mar. 29, 1921 - Apr. 5, 1921
  - Grand Trunk Railroad, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 49)
    Code No. MC-54-14-16; Apr. 5, 1921 - Apr. 16, 1921
  - Blue Ridge Railroad, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 50)
    Code No. MC-426-14-17; Apr. 16 - Apr. 27
  - Mobile Yards, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 51)
    Code No. MC-0-14-18; Apr. 25
  - Regional Boards of Adjustments, 1920-1934 (Box 111, Folder 52)
    Code No. MC-0-14-19; Feb. 21, 1920 - Feb. 23, 1934
  - Central Vermont System Federation No. 93, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 53)
    Code No. MC-21-14-20; Sept. 27-30
  - Estimated Expense of Negotiating Agreements with Separate Railroads - Circular - Conference committee, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 54)
    Code No. MC-0-14-24; Jan. 26, 1921 - Apr. 11, 1921
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 55)
    Code No. MC-74-14-25; Jan. 31, 1922 - May 20, 1922
  - Big Four and Cincinnati Northern Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 56)
    Code No. MC-6-14-29; Feb. 4, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Southern Pacific Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 57)
    Code No. MC-157-14-30; Jan. 6, 1922 - Jun. 3, 1922
  - Orient System's Federation Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 58)
    Code No. MC-84-14-31; Feb. 8, 1922 - May 20, 1922
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 59)
    Code No. MC-93-14-32; Feb. 3, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Rutland Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 60)
    Code No. MC-152-14-33; Feb. 13, 1922 - May 5, 1922
  - Arizona and Eastern Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 61)
    Code No. MC-3-14-35; Feb. 6, 1922 - Jun. 14, 1922
  - Atlanta Joint Terminal Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 111, Folder 62)
    Code No. MC-7-14-36; Aug. 15, 1921 - Apr. 14, 1922
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 63)
    Code No. MC-22-14-37; Feb. 11, 1922 - Jun. 2, 1922
  - Lackawanna System Federation No. 78, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 64)
    Code No. 39-14-38; Feb. 15, 1922 - May 20, 1922
  - Rock Island System Federation, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 65)
    Code No. MC-37-14-41; Feb. 17, 1922 - Mar. 24, 1922
  - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 66)
    Code No. MC-113-14-42; Feb. 9, 1922 - May 31, 1922
  - Green Bay and Western Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 67)
    Code No. MC-65-14-43; Feb. 17, 1922 - May 31, 1922
  - Pere Marquette Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 68)
    Code No. MC-130-14-44; Feb. 16, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis and Affiliated Lines, 1922-1923 (Box 111, Folder 69)
    Code No. MC-159-14-45; Feb. 22, 1922 - Oct. 24, 1923
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 70)
    Code No. MC-182-14-46; Jan. 17, 1922 - May 10, 1922
  - Denver and Rio Grande Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 71)
    Code No. MC-38-14-47; Feb. 22, 1922 - May 4, 1922
  - Tennessee Central Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 72)
    Code No. MC-174-14-48; Feb. 14, 1922 - Jul. 7, 1922
  - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 73)
    Code No. MC-30-14-49; Feb. 26, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Ann Arbor Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 74)
    Code No. MC-5-14-50; Feb. 13, 1922 - Jun. 13, 1922
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 75)
    Code No. MC-86-14-51; Feb. 16, 1922 - Jun. 16, 1922
  - New York Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 111, Folder 76)
    Code No. MC-86-14-52; Dec. 14, 1921 - May 11, 1922
  - New York, Ontario and Western Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 77)
    Code No. MC-120-14-53; Feb. 26, 1922 - May 8, 1922
  - System Federation No. 121 - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 78)
    Code No. MC-169-14-54; Feb. 28, 1922 - Mar. 15, 1922
  - St. Louis and Southwestern Railway, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 79)
    Code No. MC-160-14-55; Mar. 2, 1922 - Jun. 5, 1922
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 80)
    Code No. MC-190-14-56; Mar. 4, 1922 - May 26, 1922
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 81)
    Code No. MC-9-14-57; Mar. 3, 1922 - Jun. 9, 1922
  - System Federation No. 48, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 82)
    Code No. MC-15-14-58; Mar. 3, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Memphis Union Station Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 111, Folder 83)
    Code No. MC-307-14-59; May 31, 1921 - Jun. 7, 1922
  - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 84)
    Code No. MC-160-14-60; Mar. 9, 1922 - Mar. 27, 1922
  - Texas and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Code No. MC-169-14-61; Feb. 23, 1922 - Nov. 10, 1923
  - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Code No. MC-78-14-62; Mar. 3, 1922 - Mar. 16, 1922
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Code No. MC-108-14-63; Feb. 20, 1922 - Jun. 2, 1922
  - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Code No. MC-47-14-64; Mar. 30, 1922 - Jun. 23, 1922
  - Georgia Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-62-14-65; Feb. 13, 1922 - Jun. 17, 1922
  - Railroad Employees Dept. Convention - Strike Ballots, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    Code No. MC-0-14-67; Apr. 25, 1922 - Jun. 27, 1922
  - Division No. 3 Convention, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    Code No. MC-0-14-68; Apr. 24, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Letter to all General Chairmen from B.M. Jewell re Conferences on working conditions in connection with addendum to Decision 222, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    Code No. MC-0-14-69; Apr. 27
  - Pennsylvania and West Virginia Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-138-14-70; Apr. 27-29
  - District Lodge No. 32, International Association of Machinists, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    Code No. MC-0-14-71; Apr. 27 - May 2
  - St. L.&W. Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-173-14-72; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 1, 1922
  - Erie Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-48-14-73; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 2, 1922